=Born Again=
=Episode 4=
Gu Xiaotang,
have you no shame?
Shut up!
Isn't that Gu Xiaotang?
Who's that guy next to her?
See? They're holding hands.
Isn't Gu Xiaotang getting married?
Could he be the other man?
It was urgent just now.
- I...
- No...
So, well...
Do you have any more lollipops?
No.
It's okay.
I'll just faint then.
So next,
where are we going?
So we've broken the loop?
I'm at your place now.
It should be safe, right?
Unless
you're the mastermind behind all this.
These blueberries are too sour.
Why are you looking at me?
I'll go make you a salad.
(Did I trust him too easily?)
(Your left waist wound
hasn't healed right.)
No heavy exercise yet.
Here.
Aren't you hypoglycemic?
(How does he know
I had a waist reduction surgery?)
(And that I'm prone to hypoglycemia?)
(That's so weird.)
(So many lollipops.)
Do you usually
like to eat candy?
No, I don't.
(Body Textbook)
(This is...)
(Could it be
that I was his target from the start?)
(He couldn't be trying to...)
Mei, I'll give you an address.
Come pick me up.
What are you doing?
Stay back!
- Xiaotang, what's wrong? What happened?
- Don't follow me!
I'll smash you, you creep!
- I'll kill you!
- Xiaotang!
- Are you misunderstanding something?
- Peeping Tom!
Stalker!
I'll kill you!
Why are you looking at me?
Do you want to take a photo too?
Let's take a photo together.
Look at the camera.
Three, two, one.
Cheese!
Why not look at the camera?
It's yours.
When I become
a shining superstar someday,
this will be a collector's edition.
Homework's on you today.
Ye Shen.
Not my fault I didn't recognize you.
It's mainly your fault.
You've just changed so much.
Back in school,
you didn't talk much.
I even thought you might be mute.
But now,
you can fight,
and even kiss.
It's so misleading.
You...
Stop drinking.
Wait.
You...
Does it hurt?
I didn't hold back.
It's all bruised.
It's fine.
Ye Shen,
I haven't even asked...
You haven't answered me yet.
Tell me.
After I dropped out of high school
to become a trainee,
we haven't met since, right?
So today,
why did you show up at my wedding?
Just passing by.
It looked lively, so I...
Passing by?
Passing by.
Still got chemistry.
We
were high school classmates,
and now we're
trapped in this loop together.
We've got chemistry, right?
Actually, I wasn't passing by.
I wanted to see
if the girl
who wanted a perfect life back then
had her wish fulfilled.
(In the future,)
I will definitely become
the most famous superstar in the world,
and have a perfect life.
Believe it or not?
I do.
(Later on,)
- (I heard about you dropping out.)
- Did you hear?
Gu Xiaotang dropped out.
I heard she's going
to be some kind of star.
She's just going to work to make money.
I heard her mom is sick.
She signed a ten-year contract
with a talent agency.
(Seven years passed)
(before I saw you again.)
Look, is that Gu Xiaotang?
I bought her products.
She's an influencer now.
(After all these years,)
(you haven't changed much.)
(Still as clever as ever.)
Use it for three months,
and my skin's so dewy and plump.
A true all-nighter savior.
Sensitive skin friendly.
And today
we have an amazing deal on this one.
Buy one, get one free.
We'll have more benefits for you.
So that's all for today's livestream.
(Two more hours of streaming)
Almost...
I see there's a product
we haven't shared with you all.
(Though everyone keeps saying)
(nobody hustles harder than you,)
(I always feel like you're exhausted)
(and upset.)
(Because when you're unset,
you rub your ears.)
(Later on,)
(I heard that you were getting married.)
(Gu Xiaotang and Lu Qingyuan)
I really want to know if you're happy.
(Did you marry someone you love?)
So,
I sneaked in.
What... What's wrong?
How did I almost fall asleep?
No.
I need to go home now.
You forgot?
Once I fall asleep,
the loop will restart.
- I'm going home.
- You are okay?
I'm fine.
Just now when I fell asleep,
I vaguely heard you talking to me.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
I need to go home now.
I'll see you off then.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪